

About Me

A self-taught and creative Frontend Developer specializing in building web applications using React.js. I have extensive experience in creating responsive and visually appealing user interfaces.

Contact

- +212 672397065
- ayoub-ok147@hotmail.fr
- Morocco, Marrakesh,

於 Skills

- Programming Languages: JavaScript (React.js), HTML, CSS.
- Frameworks: React.js, Redux.
- · Development Tools: Git, npm, Webpack.
- RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN
- · Working with APIs.
- Bootstrap, tailwind, Materiel UI

Language

- Arabic
- English

Ayoub Baslam

Frontend Developer -React.Js



Education

2021-2022

UDEMY - JONAS SCHMEDTMANN

The Complete JavaScript Course 2023

2022 - 2023

UDEMY - YAROB AL MOSTAFA

React is - Hooks - Redux - State - Router

Experience

2021 - 2022

 Developed and designed responsive user interfaces using React.js HTML, and CSS

2022 - 2023

 Built and maintained efficient and innovarive web applications using React.js and its libraries.

2022 - 2023

 Integrated applications with APIs and handled received data.